<Mod>
	<Name>Playable Character Pack</Name>
<Version>1.3</Version>
<InstallationPath>PlayableCharacterPack</InstallationPath>
<ReleaseDate>5 May 2025</ReleaseDate>
<Author>Tirlititi and WarpedEdge</Author>
<Description>Adds new playable characters to the roster
	Current List of playable characters [Name/ID]:
	- Kuja (12)
	- Fratley (13)
	- Lani (14)
	- Haagen (15)
	- Kohel (16)
	- Aria (17)
	- Ophelia (18)

	You can press Alt+F2 or Ctrl+Alt+Shift+F2 if on Linux in-game to access the party menu (changing the party at any time is a feature of Memoria, not related to this mod).

	You should set the priority of this mod to be higher than the priority of the Moguri mod but lower than other mods.

	For Modders: Besides the characters ID ranges listed above, We use the 10000-10999 range for Commands, Spells, Items, etc. For mod compatibility, please use a range other mods are not using unless you are overwriting them on purpose. </Description>

<PatchNotes>Requires Memoria v2025.04.19 or later


	Release 1.3 Adds the following characters with their own unique abilities and skills:
	- Haagen: Typical Pluto Knight model wielding a Sword
	- Kohel: Different Pluto Knight model wielding a Spear
	- Aria: Different Alexandrian Knight using a different model wielding Claws
	- Ophelia: Typical Alexandrian Knight model wielding a Sword

	New Costume:
	- Blank - Pluto Knight Armor

	Upcoming Release 1.4 will feature:
	- Dan: Burmecian soldier Dan wielding Daggers
	- Jeame: A Cleyra Dancer wielding Rackets
	- Puck: Our little rat prince wielding both rods and staves

	Future Release 1.5 will feature:
	- Mikoto: Female Terran like Zidane wielding Daggers
	- Gerome: Male Terran like Zidane wielding a Axe
	- Ruby: Tantalus crew member wielding a Racket
	- Baku: Leader of Tantalus wielding a Sword

	Currently this mod is not compatible with Trance Seek, but I plan on getting it to eventually.</PatchNotes>
<Category>Gameplay</Category>
<Website>https://steamcommunity.com/app/377840/discussions/0/3497635791229563331/</Website>
<DownloadUrl>https://www.dropbox.com/s/b5pbed8pshd3l4t/PC_PlayableCharacterPack.zip?dl=1</DownloadUrl>
<PreviewFile>Preview.png</PreviewFile>
<PreviewFileUrl>https://i.imgur.com/vZ8DbNQ.png</PreviewFileUrl>
<Header>Costumes</Header>
<SubMod>
	<Name>Zidane Pluto outfit</Name>
<InstallationPath>Costumes/ZidaneArmor</InstallationPath>
<Description>When enabled, Zidane's battle model will wear Pluto knight armor from the story.</Description>
</SubMod>
<SubMod>
	<Name>Garnet White Mage robe</Name>
<InstallationPath>Costumes/GarnetHooded</InstallationPath>
<Description>When enabled, Garnet's battle model will wear the traditional White Mage robe.</Description>
</SubMod>
<SubMod>
<Name>Blank Pluto outfit</Name>
<InstallationPath>Costumes/BlankArmor</InstallationPath>
<Description>When enabled, Blank's battle model will wear the Pluto knight armor from the story.</Description>
</SubMod>
</Mod>
