<Mod>
	<Name>Playable Character Pack</Name>
	<Version>1.6.2</Version>
	<InstallationPath>PlayableCharacterPack</InstallationPath>
	<ReleaseDateOriginal>9 Nov 2022</ReleaseDateOriginal>
	<ReleaseDate>23 June 2025</ReleaseDate>
	<Author>Tirlititi and WarpedEdge</Author>
	<Description>Adds new playable characters to the roster.

Please Note:
- Still only playable in US Language only (will be fixed in a later release)
- Requires Memoria v2025.05.11 or later
- Currently this mod is not compatible with Trance Seek, but I plan on getting it to eventually
- Currently Alternate Fantasy will have some nuances like Cheat Fate, Fidget, Auto-Protect/Shell missing (this will be fixed in a later update of PCP)

Currently, these characters are added:
- Kuja
- Fratley
- Lani
- Haagen
- Kohel
- Aria (Alexandrian soldier)
- Ophelia (Alexandrian soldier)
- Dan
- Jeame (Cleyra dancer)
- Puck
- Mikoto *NEW*
- Gerome (Genome) *NEW*
- Ruby *NEW*
- Baku *NEW*

You can press Alt+F2 or Ctrl+Alt+Shift+F2 if on Linux in-game to access the party menu (changing the party at any time is a feature of Memoria, not related to this mod).

Special Thanks for their important help:
- LucyHale00 for bug reporting
- HsienkoMegatonDrop for bug reporting
- aron for bug reporting
- Emeiru (support)
- Hope (scripting)
- faospark (concept art)
- samtoki (character portraits)
- DV (ability sequences and features)

You should set the priority of this mod to be higher than the priority of the Moguri mod but lower than other mods, but until Alternate Fantasy's next update, put this mod's priority above it</Description>
	<PatchNotes>
	------[1.6.2]------

	- Fixed Gerome's wild strike to accurate use same script as darkside

	------[1.6.1]------

	- Fixed major bug causing custom status' to inflict negative ones instead
	- adjusted item priority of axes
	- added items to shops that were missable in disc 4
	- fixed Baku's sneeze accuracy

	Bug Fixes:
	- Aria Thunderstrike stuck to Thunder gloves when she cannot equip them (Now moved to Mythril Armlet)
	- Jeame's Debilitation description fixed as well as the effect correctly lowering ATK/MATK
	- Jeame's dance text added when casted
	- Jeame's Dance of Life not targeting KO
	- Dan's main attack is now Mug like originally intended
	- Puck not being able to learn Stona due to it being stuck to rackets/flutes (Healing Rod now teaches it)
	- Puck not being able to learn Aero/Aera; Added to Stardust and Asura's Rod</PatchNotes>
	<Category>Gameplay</Category>
	<Website>https://steamcommunity.com/app/377840/discussions/0/3497635791229563331/</Website>
	<DownloadUrl>https://github.com/WarpedEdge/ffix-mod-projects/releases/download/PCP-v1.6.2/PlayableCharacterPack.zip</DownloadUrl>
	<PreviewFile>Preview.png</PreviewFile>
	<PreviewFileUrl>https://i.imgur.com/LdMuKh1.png</PreviewFileUrl>
	<Header>Costumes</Header>
	<SubMod>
		<Name>Zidane Pluto outfit</Name>
		<InstallationPath>Costumes/ZidaneArmor</InstallationPath>
		<Description>When enabled, Zidane's battle model will wear Pluto knight armor from the story.</Description>
	</SubMod>
	<SubMod>
		<Name>Garnet White Mage robe</Name>
		<InstallationPath>Costumes/GarnetHooded</InstallationPath>
		<Description>When enabled, Garnet's battle model will wear the traditional White Mage robe.</Description>
	</SubMod>
	<SubMod>
		<Name>Blank Pluto outfit</Name>
		<InstallationPath>Costumes/BlankArmor</InstallationPath>
		<Description>When enabled, Blank's battle model will wear the Pluto knight armor from the story.</Description>
	</SubMod>
</Mod>
